Nah Trang , Vietnam 01-07-1972 , 1 : 30 AM
Come in , Butterfly .
Donkey three , come in , Butterfly .
Butterfly , come in , Donkey three .
Come in , Butterfly .
Go and report this , hurry !
We 're dying like hell !
Butterfly , Butterfly .
Come in , Donkey three . Come in , Donkey three . Over .
Who the f * * * is this ?
Donkey three was your unit , right ?
No , it 's not possible .
My men are all dead !
Then how is that they sent a transmission 3 days ago !
And it 's the 3rd time this month !
Who the f * * * sent the transmissions then ?
I swear , they 're all dead !
I collected their tags myself .
With these hands !
Who did this to you ? Viet Cong ?
There are no f * * * ing Viet Cong in R-Point !
I watched all of them f * * * ing die !
I 'm telling you , this is paradise !
What ? I 'm coming !
Lieutenant CHOI !
Hello , how are you ?
Alright .
Damn , she 's hot !
Sleep .
Don 't shoot .
Don 't move !
Private KIM !
F * * * , I saw this coming !
I 'll take it .
It came earlier than I expected .
Investigation Division , yes sir !
He 's here , sir .
Two damn decorations !
You 're an excellent soldier CHOI .
And the only survivor of the battle at Honbawoo ...
I heard you 're ill .
I 'm fine now . I 'll be released in 2 days .
Have some tea .
It 's Ho Chi Minh 's favorite .
No , thank you , sir .
You never go to battle without shedding some blood ...
whether it 's yours or the enemy 's .
That 's why no one likes being in your platoon , right ?
Confidential
This is a list of the men who went missing 6 months ago .
This case requires a competent leader like you .
I 'd like to have my old platoon back .
According to us , yesterday 's incident never happened .
Is this an order ?
Congratulations on being back in the fight .
What the ... ? That 's disgusting !
Move your hands !
He 's clean .
What 're you here for ?
I traded my medical certificate for 50 bucks .
Why ?
50 bucks is enough to buy a cow .
And I want to buy my mom one .
A f * * * ing cow .
Sergeant JANG , 18 years old ?
That means you were recruited at 16 ?
16 ?
Yes , sir .
The recruitment documents were issued to my old brother ...
And I used them to enlist , without my family knowing .
He 's a f * * * ing kid ?
He fooled us all ?
You saying a f * * * ing kid like that
is the same rank as me ?
What 's going on ?
Can 't go home until we get cleaned up .
What 's the f * * * ing big deal ? So we got syphilis .
My family 's expecting to see me at the port .
No need to give you a long speech .
Once again ,
the region you 're assigned to is a non-combat zone .
A f * * * ing ' non-combat ' zone .
If you complete the mission ,
you 're going home on a f * * * ing " plane " .
Remember , it ' a plane , not a ship .
You 'll have hot stewardesses serving you juice , get it ?
Sergeant PARK , I 'm in !
Corporal BYUN !
Sergeant OH !
Double check all your gear !
Attention !
Salute , sir ,
I 'm Sergeant JIN !
CHOI Tae-in , First Lieutenant !
These are the men , sir .
Attention .
That 's alright . At ease .
At ease .
When are we going ?
Just relax , man .
You know that bastard !
You mean Sergeant JIN ?
He 's a cold-blooded killer . Been here for 3 years and ...
I 've seen a picture of him holding a VC soldier 's head cut off !
You dumb ass ! Everybody does that crap here !
Have you ?
Damn right , was no big deal . Nothing scares me !
Cut that f * * * ing racket out !
Just a few days away from going home too .
f * * * .
Pisses me off .
It 's not looking good .
We got a moron and a psychopath !
We 're f * * * ing doomed !
I 'll be back in a week ! Hear me ?
You believe this f * * * ing weather ?
It 's my first time on a ship .
You were a pen pusher , right ? No , then what missions ...
How about a souvenir photo ?
Sounds good ! Damn good idea !
You think you 're here on a picnic or something ?
No , sir .
Why not ? Let 's do it .
Sure , it 's damn good !
Just wait !
Here we go , one , two , three !
R-POINT : Day 1
These f * * * ing mosquitoes !
Damn , I 'm missing the welcome home party at Pusan !
Cease fire !
It 's coming from 11 : 00 .
Sergeant JANG , get the f * * * out of there !
I can 't .
Move , son of a bitch !
Run like hell , on my count !
1 , 2 ...
Corporal JOH , give it to me !
Cover me !
These bastards have been dead for ages .
Search her .
What 's this ?
If you touch a dead person 's things , your fingers 'll rot off .
I just had a look !
Take care of her .
You f * * * ing baby ! You can 't do it , can you ?
Corporal LEE , finish her .
You pussy . Don 't have the balls , huh ?
Let me do this .
Move out .
Sergeant JIN , take the lead .
This is where R-Point begins .
Let 's take a break .
Break time .
We almost there ?
Yeah .
Give me a smoke then .
What ? A gravestone !
What does ... it say ?
Hey , read it out aloud .
How weird ! I don 't like this .
There used to be a lake here .
Cut the crap ! There 's nothing but trees .
" Hundreds of years ago , the Chinese killed Vietnamese
and dumped them into the lake . "
" After that they filled the lake , and built a temple on it . "
Bullshit ! You lying son of a bitch !
That 's why it 's so foggy .
" Wherever you go , I 'll be there . "
" lf you have blood on your hands ... "
I can 't read the rest .
You 're a f * * * ing story teller .
No , he 's right .
Let 's go .
This shit 's creepy !
What the ... ? " bloody hand are " ... what ?
I 've had blood on my hands , so what ?
Hey , Corporal LEE !
What ?
Don 't disrespect it .
Don 't be a pussy .
I ain 't afraid of shit .
Hey asshole , wait up !
Hurry !
" Can 't go back "
Sergeant PARK . You 're in the military band , right ?
Mr. Sex Machine PARK is all dried up in Vietnam .
So you blow ... the bugle or what ?
You idiot ! " The bugle " ?
It 's called a Saxophone !
If you play one of those , you can 't get it up , right ?
What asshole said that ?
My cock 's got more power than any of yours !
That 's why all the hot bitches wanna f * * * me .
There isn 't a single vocalist in Korea I haven 't screwed .
I 'm the god father of the bitches !
You wanna stand up and let the f * * * ers know we 're here ?
No , sir .
One , two , one , two ...
Butterfly , come in . Mole three has met Romeo , over .
Butterfly .
Hand it over when you get through .
Why are you cutting up your clothes ?
You have no idea ? Never been on a mission , right ?
We believe we can survive by doing this .
Sorry , sir .
What a nutcase .
What did you do before coming to Vietnam ?
It might freak you out .
I washed corpses .
Bullshit !
He means it .
Don 't try to f * * * with me !
His father 's an undertaker .
You saw him reading Chinese characters well .
' Cause they use Chinese characters a lot in that line .
Is he serious ?
Yes , sir .
I got a strange feeling . Something 's not right here .
What do you mean ?
No sunshine , it 's damp with moisture , and foggy .
It 's not a good place for graves .
It 's not good for people , living or dead , except maybe ...
Except who ?
Well , there must be some .
I 'm asking you , " who " ?
Ghosts .
Cut the crap , you son of a bitch !
I 'm out of here . How about you ?
Hey , wait up !
Corporal JOH .
Wait up !
Assholes !
Salute !
You scared the hell out of me , you idiot !
Lieutenant .
It 's working now .
Mole three , come in , Butterfly .
Donkey Three has met Romeo .
We 've reached the check point .
Our coordinates are D270W279
We are in section R5 ,
reporting at 06 : 30 . And from 07 : 00 ...
Room one first floor , clear .
Basement , clear !
Fucking made in the USA .
It 's a piece of shit , here .
What 's this ?
Come on !
Hey , wait up !
Our mission is to find
their whereabouts , dead or alive .
The surrounding area covering 3.5 km
from this spot is " R-Point " .
This region is considered
to be " sacred " to the Vietnamese .
Remember , we only have 7 days to complete our mission , and cleanly .
We 'll move in 2 units .
What battalion did the missing men belong to ?
It 's f * * * ing irrelevant to you !
Battalion 53 !
Battalion 5 ... 3 ?
You 're from the 53rd , right ? You know them then ?
Bullshit !
I don 't know shit about them .
Today , Sergeant JIN 's unit is scouting R-5 ,
the rest of you search this area .
Move !
The sooner you find them , the sooner you go home .
It 's been long enough for them to turn into ghosts or something by now .
Dammit !
We 're basically a bunch of chumps , right , Sergeant OH ?
Sergeant OH ?
Sergeant OH !
Sergeant OH .
Where are you ?
Sergeant OH !
This isn 't funny , quit it !
Sergeant OH ! How many times do I have to call ... .
You freaked me out ! Why didn 't you answer me ?
Jung-Suk , wait for me
Are you listening to me ?
Quit messing with me !
I don 't like this shit , sir !
Corporal LEE !
Let 's take a break .
What are you eating ?
What 're you grubbing on ?
You f * * * ing brat !
Here , have all you want .
It 's antibiotics , you asshole .
Fuck you !
For your information , it doesn 't help .
What ? Missing ?
Give me the map .
What 's your location ?
Got it .
We 're heading for R-6 , we 'll meet up there !
Corporal JOH !
We 're here to find the missing men and one of us is missing ? Shit !
It 's so creepy !
What 's this smell ?
I almost shot you !
You came out of nowhere !
Have you found him ?
Not yet , sir .
Lieutenant !
I 'm telling the truth !
You asshole !
Sergeant JIN !
The Lieutenant saved your ass , you 're lucky .
Alright , we 've got lights !
What ?
" Jung-sook , wait for me " is written on your helmet , right ?
What 'd you say ?
Have you f * * * ing lost it ?
What 's your problem ?
What 're you doing ?
Cut the " Jung-sook " shit out !
I 'm right , ain 't I ?
You son of a bitch !
What 's going on ?
Who are those bastards ?
What ? Yankees ?
How come they 're here this late ?
Stay calm .
I 'm Sergeant First Class Beck from CE .
I 'm Lieutenant CHOI .
Anyway , what made you come up here at night ?
We can only come up here at night , Lieutenant .
We can 't operate the chopper in the day because of fog .
We usually come up here every four days to check the batteries .
Is that your camp , Lieutenant ?
Why ?
Is this building your governmental property ?
I ain 't got nothing to do with the mother f * * * ing U.S government
Let me tell you guys something .
Keep your rusty dick beaters off my shit in this room .
Don 't worry .
What made you come up here ?
We came up to look for my soldiers .
You gotta be shitting me ... right ?
We came to find our soldiers who 've been missing for the last six months .
You know it was a retreat for French soldiers ?
Yeah , a retreat for French soldiers .
Fuck , a lot of French soldiers were exterminated here .
It all happened so fast .
But I can sure as hell tell you one thing , it wasn 't the VC that did it .
Hell during that time the VCs didn 't exist .
There 's nothing alive here in R-point .
Neither ROK soldiers nor VCs can survive here .
What do you mean by that ?
You haven 't heard the rumors about this place ?
What rumors ?
Don 't worry about it .
Hey , good bye guys !
Hey Sergeant , don 't waste your time on these fools .
Goodbye , come again !
Let 's go .
Thanks for the beer .
Hey come on Sergeant , let 's go .
You know why my soldiers are urging me ?
They wanna make a bet as soon as possible .
Bet ?
That in four days when we come back , you won 't still be alive .
What do you mean ?
I already told you . This is R-point .
No one can survive .
Let me make myself clear .
Don 't touch my shit on the 2nd floor .
By the way , good luck .
You 're gonna need it , Lieutenant .
Salute !
Have a drink . No , thank you , sir .
Sit down and drink .
Thank you , sir .
Hey , I found this . Try and fix it .
You think you can ?
Sure , sir .
You can ?
Salute !
Is it working ?
Local transmissions are fine ,
but not with headquarters .
Is the transmitter fine ?
Yes .
By the way , is a French unit stationed nearby ?
French army ?
I got a transmission from Jacques ... a French army corporal .
He said that he 's in the army with his twin brother Paul .
What the hell are you talking about ?
We 're the only ones in this area .
No , he said his unit is stationed nearby and ...
that he 's dropping by sometime soon .
You speak French ?
No , sir . Are you trying to mess with Lieutenant ?
Get some more sleep .
Watch it , kid .
Come here , you son of a bitch !
What 's with you ? You asshole !
You were f * * * ing lying , right ?
About what ?
About the helmet shit !
" Jung-sook , wait for me " ?
Yeah , it was yours , right ?
Who the f * * * told you about that ?
About that ? About what ?
How did you know that bastard came to Vietnam ?
Got no idea what you 're talking about !
You sneaky shit .
How come you knew the helmet story ?
What 's with you ?
I saw it myself !
Not more bullshit , you bitch !
No way , it 's not possible .
Don 't even think about messing with me ! Spit it out !
Are you f * * * ing drunk ?
I 've had enough of this shit already !
Tell me the damn truth , come on !
That helmet belongs to ...
one of missing bastards .
The ones we 're here for .
How many more nights do we gotta get through , if we survive tonight ?
Five nights , sir .
No sweat ! We got shit to worry about !
Just 5 f * * * ing nights ? I 'm gonna make it for sure !
What 's that ?
Oh , the Ventures !
You fixed it ?
Oh , baby , the Ventures ! Come on !
We 're f * * * ing dying !
Fuck !
Don 't come any closer !
Don 't come any closer ! I don 't ...
No , No !
Damn ! I still got the goose bumps .
What the f * * * was that anyway ?
You think I got a clue ?
Shithead !
What 're you doing ?
I got a question .
What 's that stench you always got ?
What the f * * * are you talking about ?
If I stink , you smell like shit !
No ,
something 's going on !
What ?
You 're posted in the kitchen !
You 've crossed the f * * * ing line , jerk .
You realize you 're insulting he king of dangerous missions in Vietnam ?
What a joke ! Sergeant Cook ?
What ?
This is some news !
Everybody 's gotta know .
If you do , I 'll kill you , asshole .
Oh , you will ? Alright , go ahead .
What ? You scared ?
Hey !
Just do me a favor .
What ?
I 'm begging you .
Don 't come any closer !
I don 't . No , No !
What is it you got there ?
Damn , what 's the problem ?
I 'm asking you ! My daughter 's photo , so what ?
Let me see .
You 're such an asshole .
She 's the most beautiful thing in the world !
How is it that you have syphilis with such a cute kid back home ?
You f * * * ing loser !
Watch your mouth , kid !
You 'd have to have joined up earlier if you wanna talk shit .
If you say one word , you 're dead !
I 'm not f * * * ing joking , got it ?
What 's that ?
Hey , Private JUNG !
Private JUNG !
That jerk doesn 't show any respect !
R-POINT : Day 2
Kitchen duty , huh ?
How come you know that shit ?
We 're sure lucky to have you around !
Yes , sir .
Once a cook , forever a cook .
Don 't move , I 'm gonna f * * * ing kill you .
Breakfast , please . I 'm hungry .
Sir , Private JUNG 's missing !
He was supposed to be on duty from 6 : 00 , but ...
You should 've reported it earlier .
I 'm doing now , sir !
Son of a bitch !
Fuck Sergeant JIN ! To hell with him !
Fuck !
Just 2 weeks away from being discharged . I 'm screwed !
Does it hurt ?
Hey .
Go and take one more look around .
You mean alone ?
I 'm not in the mood right now .
I promise to hook you up with a hot chick back in Seoul .
You 're not lying , right ?
You got my f * * * ing word .
What 's this ?
I can trust you , right ?
Don 't worry about it , just do your job .
When I 'm back in Seoul ...
Leave it to the sex machine PARK .
You 're gonna hook me up with a hot chick ?
What the f * * * ?
Viet congs are around .
We getting through to headquarters yet ?
Sorry , sir , not yet .
Lieutenant !
Our mission is to find the missing men .
Keep that in mind .
Sergeant OH .
Yes , sir !
You 're curious , aren 't you ?
Yes , sir ?
I want to have a look at his face .
What , sir ?
Set up a booby trap , kid .
Yes , sir .
Everything 's f * * * ed up around here .
What is ?
Just do your job , corpse cleaner .
Where was he from ?
You mean ... Private JUNG ?
When you were out scouting with him ...
Did he say anything ?
Was he in our unit ? I don 't remember .
Which battalion did he belong to ?
Hey , kid ! Give this to the Lieutenant .
Poor kid ! Whatever happens ,
we 're gonna get back alive !
What the f * * * ?
Hey , you son of a bitch ...
get me Captain PARK !
Make it quick , asshole !
Captain PARK here . Lieutenant CHOI , sir !
Are you f * * * ing with me ?
What do you mean , sir ?
Are you screwing this mission up ?
Private JUNG 's one of the missing men !
What ?
Lieutenant , have you f * * * ing lost it ?
Listen to me !
JUNG is one of the men you 're there to look for !
I don 't understand , sir .
You a f * * * ing idiot ?
How many are in your unit now ?
We got one down , and 9 left , sir .
You 're f * * * ing out of your mind for sure .
You started the mission with 9 , got it ?
I have the mission file in front of me right now .
You were 9 to begin with !
You mean you picked up a ghost ?
You 're joking , right ?
Do I sound like I 'm f * * * ing joking ?
Give me Sergeant JIN !
Are you listening to me , Lieutenant CHOI ?
It 's bizarre , but ...
I don 't remember his face .
I mean Private JUNG .
He was with us at the dock , right ?
What ?
He wasn 't with us from the start ...
but I remember he was there at the beach .
You dumbass , what 're you talking about ?
He was with us when we were taking the picture .
I don 't remember seeing him at the dock .
Good , I wanna be in it too .
Okay , one more time !
You take the it .
You know how to use the camera ?
Wind it .
Enough already , I don 't wanna hear any more !
Sergeant OH !
Did you get it yet ?
Oh , for f * * * ' s sake .
Be patient , I 'll get it in a couple of days .
You take care of this .
Make sure you get it .
You know it 's for my girl , Jung-sook .
I 'm sick of your Jung-sook stories .
Aren 't you going on a mission ?
Hey , hurry up !
Take care .
See you soon !
Jung-sook , wait for me .
You think those assholes can handle it on their own , sir ?
That 's why I put you on the mission .
Do whatever it takes to close the case .
R-POINT : Day 3
You knew the whole time , didn 't you !
Cut it out !
Where 're you going ?
Going to shit , goddammit !
A lot of French soldiers were exterminated here
It all happened so fast .
I got a transmission from Jacques and ...
Paul and Jacques rest in peace here .
he said his twin brother Paul is in the same army .
Don 't touch it !
You like this camera , don 't you ?
You got any idea how much I paid for it ?
It cost me 4 months salary .
But I know it 's not yours .
You got it without getting one drop of blood on your hands ?
You motherf * * * er !
Who are you ?
He 's on the edge .
Oh , no ! You 're dead , it can 't be you !
I saw the photo .
Why didn 't you tell them he was one of the missing ...
I don 't care whether he 's f * * * ing missing or not .
Don 't tell the men about it .
What ?
We need to bring them back alive .
It 's the booby trap !
No ...
Sergeant OH !
Believe me , I didn 't do it on purpose .
He must have triggered the trap .
Hang on , Sergeant OH !
What happened ? Snap out of it !
Sergeant OH !
Come on !
Oh , please , don 't kill me , I 'm begging you .
I didn 't mean to lie ... Forgive me !
What 're you doing ?
Save me !
I 'm sorry !
Something 's going on .
There 's gotta be something they 're not telling us .
Ghosts !
R-Point 's f * * * ing haunted !
You f * * * ing idiot !
Fucking ' Ghosts ' ?
Look around ! Open your eyes .
You see any f * * * ing ghosts ?
You son of a bitch .
All you got to do is ...
find the missing radio operator 's tags , got it ?
Any of you say a word about this ghost shit ,
and you 'll be thrown in jail .
What 're you gonna do , sir ?
Why don 't we abort this mission ?
You think they 'll believe this f * * * ing story ?
But we can 't lie to our men forever .
All we need is to find any clue about the radio operator ?
Sorry , but it doesn 't look like it 's possible .
We 'll scout this region from the spot we arrived .
Alright , then .
We should split into two groups instead of one .
Looks like we 're all on different pages ,
some like playing ball and some don 't .
R-POINT : Day 4
Fall in .
Give a status report every 30 minutes .
Once again , today we 're covering R-5 and R-2 .
Under no circumstances
will you stray from your designated zones , got it ?
Yes , sir .
Break into 2 teams .
Yes , sir !
You bugle player !
You !
Yes , sir !
And you !
Yes , sir .
Get in this line .
I want to be in your unit , sir !
I do , too , sir !
You f * * * ing pussies . You think this is a game ?
I want one more asshole !
I 'm ordering you , one more !
Enough .
Move out .
Isn 't this the way we took before ?
Let 's go to bamboo woods .
Why , sir ?
I need to check something out .
Sergeant JIN !
This is R-7 , sir .
I know .
But Lieutenant told us not to stray from ...
Shut up and come with me .
Sergeant JIN !
This must be the Lieutenant 's .
Search this area , now !
What the hell are you doing ?
You screwed us up , Lieutenant !
Corporal BYUN , look around over here .
We don 't have time , move !
What we need are tags from one of the missing men .
Sergeant !
Why isn 't the woods coming up ?
We should 've reached it by now .
What the hell 's going on ?
What does it say ?
Hey Cook , you can read it , right ?
You know ?
" ... can 't go back "
Who can 't go back ?
Lieutenant , is it true ?
Does that thing really say " ... can 't go back " ?
Mole three , come in . Mole one , do you copy ?
Mole one , do you copy ?
Mole three , come in . Mole one , come in .
Mole three , come in . Mole one .
Mole three , Mole one , do you copy ?
Sergeant JIN , where 're you going ?
I 'll be right back . Keep trying to get the reach the Lieutenant .
Lieutenant !
Aren 't these ... the Yankees we met ?
What the hell 's going on ?
Then we met their f * * * ing corpses ?
Hey , Cook , tell me the truth .
Are these the f * * * ers we met ?
Lieutenant , does that mean we 're fighting against ghosts ?
Get me Sergeant JIN on the line !
What 're we gonna ... ?
Send the transmission !
Mole one , come in , Mole three .
Mole three , do you copy ?
It 's dead .
Head back to base , on the double !
Sergeant JIN ! Sergeant !
Sergeant JIN !
Where 're you ?
What the hell is this here for ?
Which means ...
He fell off here , damn !
Private JUNG gets his head chopped off and now Sergeant OH 's dead .
I 'm sick of weird shit going on . I 'm not sticking around anymore .
Does all this mean that we can 't get out of here , sir ?
Tell me something .
What 's the first thing you wanna do when you get home ?
I wanna ...
Go on a picnic to the Royal Palace with my wife and daughter .
I 'm telling you , it 's going to happen .
Corporal JOH !
It 's the missing men !
Corporal JOH ...
Who 's there ?
Sergeant OH ?
Sergeant PARK ?
Donkey three , Butterfly , come in .
Come in , Butterfly .
We 're dying , do you copy ?
Butterfly , do you copy ?
This is Donkey three .
Come in , Butterfly .
We 're getting massacred .
Butterfly , do you copy ?
This is Donkey three !
Sergeant PARK ?
What ?
Something 's chasing us .
I told you to cut the bullshit out , asshole !
Corporal LEE !
I 'm scared ...
that OH is gonna kill me .
He blames me , I know it !
Cut the crap , you son of a bitch !
If you see something , just shoot .
Cease fire !
You son of a bitch , it 's us !
Lieutenant , are you all right ?
What the hell are you doing ?
Hey Cook , are you all right ?
Hang on !
Do something , son of a bitch !
You think I can make it ?
Yeah , don 't worry .
Don 't lie to my face , bitch !
No , you can 't die .
Calm down .
I 'm not going to die .
I won 't die before I go on a picnic with my wife and daughter ...
Get through this and I 'll treat you as my own older brother .
Please don 't die , I 'll do whatever you tell me to .
You 've finally grown up , kid .
Whatever happens ...
make it back home .
Sergeant MAH .
Hey , Cook , get up !
Don 't die on me !
I saw this coming .
You f * * * ing nut !
Sergeant JANG !
Get off !
Look , I was right !
The ghost was coming after me .
What else was I supposed to do ?
You killed him , and you 're trying to say it was a ghost ?
Let me go !
I 'm possessed by an evil spirit now !
Move out .
Mole three , come in , Butterfly .
Butterfly ...
Give it up .
Tomorrow the Americans will be here , so we can ask for help .
Come with me .
Lieutenant !
It 's a waste of time .
What 's this ?
Get this shit downstairs .
Then who were ... those Americans ?
They 're not coming .
What do you mean ?
You knew it and didn 't tell us the f * * * ing truth .
Put your weapons down .
You were in on it , weren 't you ? Kissing his ass !
Hurry up and arrest these sons of bitches .
Get this equipment downstairs .
Don 't try to f * * * with us !
What good is this junk ?
Put your weapon down .
If you come any closer , I 'll fire .
If you wanna live , follow my orders .
Hurry !
R-POINT : Day 5
Butterfly , come in , Mole three .
Do you copy ? Come in , Mole three .
Lieutenant , it 's working .
Mole three , come in , Butterfly .
Urgent . Send backup right away .
What situation ?
We need backup !
Send a chopper to R-Point right now !
It 's too dark .
05 : 50 am is the earliest we can get to you .
Cut the shit and send a f * * * ing chopper now !
We 're losing time .
Confirm , a chopper will be there by 05 : 50 ...
Butterfly !
Do you copy ? You son of a bitch !
You don 't know what the hell is going on here !
Listen carefully .
We 'll make it out of here alive .
To your stations !
Open the goddamn door !
It 's Sergeant JIN , we should let him in !
No , don 't open it !
No !
Sergeant , you 're alive , sir !
We shouldn 't have come here .
Your name and official rank .
What 're you doing , sir ?
You wanna play boss until the end , huh !
Your last chance , name and rank !
Sergeant 1st Class JIN Chang-rok , 8335107 .
Are you f * * * ing happy now , bastard ?
Sergeant .
Please help me ... get back home alive .
I was the one that found the tags ...
You promised to get me on the airplane home , so ...
You wanna live , huh ?
I don 't wanna die ,
I wanna live .
I 'm too f * * * ing young to die !
What did I do to deserve this shit ?
Step away from him !
Put your weapons down .
Corporal BYUN !
Lower your weapon .
Mole three , come in , Butterfly .
Butterfly , do you copy ?
Give it up ! The f * * * ing thing 's gone !
The chopper 's on its way .
It 's coming for sure .
Corporal LEE , your name and rank !
I 'm ordering you !
Corporal LEE Jae-pil , 8327602 .
And you !
Corporal JOH Byung-hoon , 8327603 .
Sergeant JANG !
Wake up , come on !
Sergeant JANG Young-soo , 8123018 .
They 're coming .
They 're coming , I told you !
Corporal BUYN , snap out of it !
Name and rank .
Lieutenant , they 're coming .
I 'm asking you for the last time .
Get down !
Sergeant JANG , hang on !
My eyes ...
l can 't see .
Just hang on .
Corporal LEE !
Pull yourself together !
Why are they doing this to us ?
What did we do wrong ?
We don 't f * * * ing deserve this !
We haven 't done anything
to deserve this shit !
Do you really ...
mean it ?
Oh , no !
Lieutenant !
Where are you , sir ?
I lost my tags .
Without it , my dead body can 't be sent home .
Even my ashes won 't make it home .
Just get a hold of yourself !
Just stay calm !
I lost my tags .
You 're gonna make it .
Listen to me ,
we 're going to make it back alive .
You 're just injured . You 'll be fine .
Why aren 't you afraid ?
Just believe me .
We 'll get back alive , understand ?
Lieutenant ...
Where are you ?
Sergeant JANG , take your rifle .
Take your weapon !
Aim it to the left .
More to the left .
Fire !
Sir ?
What 's going on ?
You 're there , right ?
Lieutenant !
Answer me , are you there ?
Lieutenant , you 're still there , right ?
Oh , say something , please .
Lieutenant , answer me .
You 're there , aren 't you ?
You 're fooling around , right , sir ?
I need to go back home with the money I earned .
My mom 's dying to see me !
But I 'm a little scared .
I 'm afraid my mom won 't recognize me
because
I 've changed so much .
Because I can 't ... see anything now .
My home 's too far away .
Hey , Cook ,
take your angels to the Royal Palace !
LEE , BYUN and JOH !
You bastards , stop playing tricks on me !
Damn ,
it 's time to go home , right ?
We haven 't spotted anyone , except an injured soldier ,
but he 's completely lost it .
We 've searched R-Point ,
but the other 8 haven 't been found .
We 're heading back , with the only survivor . Over !
Mole three , come in , Butterfly .
Come in , Butterfly , do you copy ?
Butterfly , please , come in .